http://www.csc.ucreative.ac.uk/privacy-policy

Home/
About Us/Meet our TeamOur TrusteesThe Crafts CommunityThe History of the Crafts Study CentreBusiness Plan 2020Policy DocumentsPress CoverageSupport Us
What's On/Visiting Us + COVID 19Current Programme
Collections/About our collectionsAccessing and Searching the CollectionsArchivesCalligraphy and LetteringCeramicsFurniture and WoodTextilesRecent acquisitions
Shop/ShopMeet the MakersONLINE BOOK SHOP
CSC Blog/
Contact/
The University Museum of Modern Crafts
Privacy Policy
Home/
About Us/Meet our TeamOur TrusteesThe Crafts CommunityThe History of the Crafts Study CentreBusiness Plan 2020Policy DocumentsPress CoverageSupport Us
What's On/Visiting Us + COVID 19Current Programme
Collections/About our collectionsAccessing and Searching the CollectionsArchivesCalligraphy and LetteringCeramicsFurniture and WoodTextilesRecent acquisitions
Shop/ShopMeet the MakersONLINE BOOK SHOP
CSC Blog/
Contact/
Privacy & Cookies Policy : Crafts Study CentreThe Crafts Study Centre takes personal data security seriously and complies with European Union data protection requirements.We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of vistors to our website. This policy outlines how we treat your personal information. If you have any questions about this policy, please contact the Crafts Study Centre (CSC) at craftscentre@uca.ac.ukThe CSC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Please check this page from time to time to ensure you are kept informed of any changes.For your protection the CSC is registered through the University for the Creative Arts under the Data Protection Act 1998 (replaced by the General Data Protection Regulations 2016 from 25 May 2018).We will never share or sell your personal data. We do not use direct marketing agents. Your data is only used when it is necessary to facilitate the delivery of goods or services such as online purchases or the delivery of our programme of events and exhibitions. This may be delivered through the following:Email Newsletter. This is delivered directly to your inbox via a secure, third party email newsletter software programme called MailChimp which is accessed by CSC staff only.You can subscribe or unsubscribe from our email newsletter any time you wish. You may also update your personal data at any time. Personal data held by us extends to that only which you have provided to us by signing up to receive our newsletter.Bi-Annual Programme of Events. This is delivered by Royal Mail through your letterbox using personal data that you have provided to us for this express purpose. We may also send you from time to time, information about our exhibition private views.You can subscribe or unsubscribe from our postal correspondance any time you wish. You may also update your personal data at any time. Personal data held by us extends to that only which you have provided to us by signing up to receive our programme of events.Contact Forms. We use return e-mail addresses to answer e-mails we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You may request the details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of this information, please write to: The Director, Crafts Study Centre, Falkner Road, Farnham, Surrey GU9 7DS. Cookies(not the edible type) allow small amounts of text to be stored on your device via your web browser. Google analytics uses session cookies which are deleted once you close your browser. Other cookies ensure that our website provides relevent information in a safe and stable environment and allow us to anonymously track our visitors journey through our website, thus enabling us to improve on your experience of our website.You can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself or your location by declining to accept cookies.Our website automatically collects some anonymous information about you automatically as you move through the site. We use this data to inform the development of our service. The information collected in this way does not contain anything that can identify you personally. It provides data about what our visitors do on the site, but not who they are. SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information held with us is secure. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Gathering of Website Data The CSC website is monitored by Squarespace and Google Analytics which gathers non-personally identifying information about your device, your visit to our website such as your general geographical location, IP address, browser type, referral source, duration of visit, and number of visits. This information helps us to better understand how visitors use our website and allows us to improve what we offer by tailoring it to visitors needs.
Home/
About Us/Meet our TeamOur TrusteesThe Crafts CommunityThe History of the Crafts Study CentreBusiness Plan 2020Policy DocumentsPress CoverageSupport Us
What's On/Visiting Us + COVID 19Current Programme
Collections/About our collectionsAccessing and Searching the CollectionsArchivesCalligraphy and LetteringCeramicsFurniture and WoodTextilesRecent acquisitions
Shop/ShopMeet the MakersONLINE BOOK SHOP
CSC Blog/
Contact/
Crafts Study Centre
Temporary Opening Hours: Tuesday to Friday 10am - 4pm until Friday 11 December 2020. Usual Opening Hours: Tuesday to Friday 10am - 5pm, Saturday 10am - 4pm, Sunday and Bank Holidays - closed. Admission: General admission to the Crafts Study Centre shop and exhibitions is free of charge. Small charges may be made for events such as artist's talks, lectures and conferences.Research visits: by appointment only. For more information or to arrange a visit, please contact Greta Bertram, Curator on 01252 891452 or email on greta.bertram@uca.ac.ukThe Crafts Study Centre is accessible for wheelchair users including automatic entrance to the building and a lift to access all floors. We have an induction loop at our reception. The Crafts Study Centre is situated at the front of the campus of the University for the Creative Arts, Farnham. Parking: We are a very short walk from two pay and display carparks both of which are served by the town centre. There is limited short-stay parking immediately outside the Crafts Study Centre doors. Directions by car: Farnham is 11 miles south-west of Guildford, Surrey and is signposted from the A3, A31, M3 and A287.  Using the Crafts Study Centre postcode of GU9 7DS will bring you to the front of the University and next to two pay and display carparks. Directions by rail: Farnham Station is approximately a 15-20 minute walk and is served by two trains per hour from and to London Waterloo. For more information please visit www.nationalrail.co.uk for timetables.  Directions by bus: It is a short level walk from the bus stop on West Street and bus No.65 from Guildford to Alton stops here.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
SUBSCRIBE
We value your support and respect your privacy. We will never share your data with third parties.
Thank you for signing up to the Crafts Study Centre newsletter. Our mailing list is GDPR compliant. You will need to confirm your subscription by clicking on the email that has been sent to you. Please check your junk folder just in case!You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time by clicking on the preferences option of the last email we sent to you.
The Crafts Study Centre is a Charitable Incorporated Organisation Foundation, registered charity number 1179008CRAFTS STUDY CENTRE, UNIVERSITY FOR THE CREATIVE ARTS,  FALKNER ROAD,  FARNHAM,  SURREY,  GU9 7DS      T +44 (0) 1252 891450    CRAFTSCENTRE@UCREATIVE.AC.UKPrivacy Policy
|
Our mailing list is compliant with GDPR regulations
|
CSC Shop Sales, Refunds and Delivery Information
